http://dominodeveloper.net/doc/privacy

Domino SharedDomino VPSDomino Dedicatedlogin
XLoginPlease enter your login credentials.Login
XCreate New AccountPlease enter your registration details.First Name  Last Name  Email Address  Username  Password  Confirm Password  Register
Privacy PolicyDomino Developer Network, Inc. (together
with its subsidiaries and affiliates,
your information, and how you can correct
any inaccuracies in the information.Information We CollectDDN collects certain information from and
about its users three ways: (i) from our web
server logs, (ii) with cookies and (iii)
directly from the user.Server LogsWhen you visit our website, DDN may collect
information to administer the site and
analyze its usage. DDN may collect
information such as:• your Internet protocol address;• the type of browser or computer you use• the number of links you click• the state or country from which you
accessed our website• the date and time of your visit• the name of your Internet service
functionality of our website.Personal Information You Give UsOn some pages of our website, users can
register to purchase products or services,
receive personalized content and participate
in surveys or forums. When you register, DDN
may ask you for some personal information.If you're purchasing products or services,
of our website and computer network.You may also be asked to disclose personal
received by mail and telephone.Finally, some pages of DDN’s website may
make chat rooms, forums, message boards,
on the bulletin boards or in the chat areas,
that information and any substantive
information disclosed in the communication
can be collected and used by third parties.
This could result in unsolicited messages
from others who post on such sites and are
beyond the control of DDN.How We Use Your InformationDDN uses the information we collect to
“opting-out” as provided for below.DDN may also provide aggregate information
policies of these companies.If you don't want to receive promotional
materials from DDN or our marketing
partners, you may opt out at any time. You may "opt out" by clicking on
of deletions.How We Protect Your InformationDDN uses technical security measures to
Sockets Layer (“SSL”) technology. However,
prior to your transmitting the information.
For that reason, we ask that you do not send
confidential information such as financial
information, social security numbers or
passwords to us through unsecured electronic
communication.Access to Your InformationDDN will share or disclosure your personal
data in four ways:• as required by law, in a matter of public
safety or policy, or as compelled by a court
of law;• with other affiliates or partners of DDN
(as described above);• with agents and contractors who use such
information on behalf of DDN or in
connection with administering or delivering
products and services on behalf of DDN; and• as needed in connection with the transfer
of business assets.Links to Other WebsitesDDN’s website contain links to sites
privacy policy posted on each site.How to Correct InaccuraciesIf you've registered with our website, you
can access and update your information
online within our conrol panel. Otherwise,
you may contact us at
info@dominodeveloper.net.Privacy Policy ChangesDDN hereby reserves the right to amend,
alter, modify, replace or suspend this
Privacy Policy, from time to time, in its
sole discretion. All such changes to this
Privacy Policy will be effective when posted
on DDN’s website.QuestionsIf you have any comments or questions
regarding this Privacy Policy please contact
DDN via email at info@dominodeveloper.net.
